SABRINA ONUMA

Plymouth, MN

Phone: (612) 214-7011 | Email: sabrina42818@gmail.com LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/sabrina-onuma Portfolio: https://sabrina-onuma.github.io/Portfolio/#

SUMMARY

Detail Oriented UX/UI Designer with a background in Project Management, Cognitive Science, and Linguistics. Certificate in UX/UI from the University of Minnesota. Extensive experience in principles of user research, user interfacing, and front-end development for Fortune 500 organizations to start-ups. Strengths in creativity, organization of information, and building projects from ideation to execution. Driven by the collaborative process with experience communicating with designers, stakeholders, marketing teams, business managers to deliver outcomes that improve customer experience across web and mobile platforms.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Technical: Programming (Python, C++, HTML5, Javascript, jQuery), Google Suite, Project Management, Trello, Slack, Zoom | **UX/UI:** User Centered Design Process, User Interface Development, Design Principles, Figma, AdobeXD, InVision, Canva, ProCreate, Web User Accessibility, and Atomic Design

RELEVANT EXPERIENCE

Project Manager2022 – PresentMenashaGolden Valley, MN

Planning and monitoring progress on materials and keeping stakeholders informed throughout the project lifecycle.

Key Accomplishments:

 Received "Total Package" recognition for thorough and adept onboarding of the Project Manager role.

Visual Designer River Valley Winter Marching Arts

2021 – Present Elk River, MN

Designed and executed eye catching visuals through props, music, and marching for audience members and competition judges.

Key Accomplishments:

• Created effective props in order to enhance the audience's experience of the show's story.

Teaching Assistant/Tutor

2019 – 2021

English, Linguistics, and Writing Studies Department

Duluth, MN

Independently created quizzes, provided feedback on all graded material, and led the lab every week. Assisted students with class material and tools used for Intro to Linguistics, Syntax, Phonetics and Phonology, and Python Programming.

Key Accomplishments:

• Received two recognitions for the Thank A Teacher program.

ADDITIONAL EXPERIENCE

Team Member, E-Commerce JoAnn Fabrics

2021 – 2022 Elk River, MN

Lead, Sign Plus Banners Great Northern Equipment Distribution, Inc.Rogers, MN

Summers of 2019 & 2020

PROJECTS

Mentor Match App | sabrina-onuma.github.io/Portfolio/images/Mentor_SlideDeck.pdf

- An app development project focused on the research of recent college grads who are ready to make the next big step into their dream career.
- My Responsibilities included: Wireframing, Prototyping, User Interviews, Empathy mapping, User Journey Mapping, User Flow Creation
- Tools Used: Trello, Miro, Figma, Google Slides

Non-Profit Website Redesign | sabrina-onuma.github.io/Portfolio/images/CHUM_SlideDeck.pdf

- A redesign for the non-profit organization CHUM focused on improving the design to make it more accessible to the community who are in need of these resources the most.
- My Responsibilities included: Accessibility Checks, Presentation/Storyboarding for Project, Usability Testing, Heuristic Evaluation, Persona creation, User Flow Creation, Value Proposition
- Tools Used: Trello, Miro, Figma, Google Slides

Market Wagon Vendor App | sabrina-onuma.github.io/Portfolio/images/MW_SlideDeck.pdf

- An app redesign focused on the new vendor experience of onboarding. Through a tutorial and sign up form, our users felt more confident to start selling with Market Wagon!
- My Responsibilities included: Project Manager, Coding, and Analytics of our app intro page, user testing, and user interfacing components
- Tools Used: Gantt Chart, Miro, Figma, HTML5, CSS, Google Analytics, Hotjar

EDUCATION

Boot Camp Certificate: University of Minnesota, Minneapolis, MN

An intensive 24-week long boot camp dedicated to User Experience, User Interfacing, and Front End Development. Skills learned consist of User-Centric Design Research, Android and IOS Design, Visual Prototyping, Wireframing, User Interface Development, and Coding interactive Web Pages.

Bachelor of Arts, Cognitive Science: University of Minnesota, Duluth, MN Magna Cum Laude

Bachelor of Science, Linguistics: University of Minnesota, Duluth, MN Magna Cum Laude